[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":62109,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":77578,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":9522,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":87106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":15926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":103037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1879,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":104920,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":109394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1564,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":110961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your r esult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5001,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":115964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1692,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":117660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3843,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":121504,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2  because  1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1061,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":122567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":127071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":2087,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":129161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the f irst num ber, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":14454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":143618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1344,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":144967,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":147871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1224,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":149099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2914,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":152015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1348,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":153366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5851,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":159219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1466,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":160689,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you  subtrac t 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4286,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":164978,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":913,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":165893,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":10996,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":176894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":15456,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":192354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8869,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":201227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1130,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":202360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":205673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1330,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":207007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inv erse of  3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2708,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":209717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":926,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":210646,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3642,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":214290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1491,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":215784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3062,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":218848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":8521,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":227373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":30860,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":258236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br  /> Howe ver, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":39728,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":297968,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":303213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1608,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":304824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0 "},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":307755,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":29314,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":337074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub >6</sub> ? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":8075,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":345153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":10450,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":355608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":360774,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":7431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":368208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining question s as acc urately as possible.","rt":10726,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":378937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":383067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1147,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":384217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":387465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":389996,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3017,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":393015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3061,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":396079,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":400711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5.  You add 4 and 1 and get 5 and 5 is less than 9 so that's your answer.","response_history":["it's 5 ","5.  You add 4 and 1 and get 5 and 5 is less than 9 so that' syour","5.  You add 4 and 1 and get 5 and 5 is less than 9 so that's your answer."],"rt":22200,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":422916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and 12 is greater than 9 so you deduct 9 and get 3","response_history":["3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and 12 is greater than 9 yo","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and 12 is greater than 9 y","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and  12 is gr eater than 9 so you deduct 9 and get e.","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and 12 is greater than 9 so you deduct 9 and get e","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and 12 is greater than 9 so you deduct 9 and get 2","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and 12 is greater than 9 so you deduct 9 and get 3"],"rt":25464,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":448383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9 is the identity number because 9 + 9 is 0","response_history":["9 is the identity number because 9 _","9 is the identity number because 9 + 9 is 0"],"rt":24586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":472972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"8","response_history":["8"],"rt":43901,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":516878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"4","response_history":["11","4"],"rt":21622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":538505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["9","0"],"rt":8571,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":547081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It is 6 because 3 plus 6 is 9  and 9-9  is 0","response_history":["It is 6 because 3 plus 6 is 9 and 9-9 is 0"],"rt":26370,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":573455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because it can be created using two numbers from 1-8","response_history":["Yes because it can be created using two di","Yes because it can be created using two d","Yes because it can be created using two numbers from 1-8"],"rt":24140,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":597600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No it is not a generator because 3 can't be made with the formula for + 9","response_history":["No it is not a generator because 3 can't be made with the formula for +9"],"rt":23369,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":620974,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes it is because 5 can be made using 5 +9 4 where that becomes 0","response_history":["Yes it is because 5 can be made using 5 _","Yes it is because 5 can be made using 5 ","Yes it is because 5 can be made using 5 +9 4 where that becomes 0"],"rt":27723,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":648701,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"NO because it can't be made with the  formula  since it is ttoo large.","response_history":["NO because it can't be made with the formula since 3 _","NO because it can't be made with the formula since 3 +9 ","NO because it can't be made with the formula since it is ttoo large."],"rt":59755,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":708460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":12269,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":720733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n -n","response_history":["0","n-n"],"rt":19110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":739847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"It is a number that will give zero","response_history":["It is a number that will give zero"],"rt":14939,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":754790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"if it is even and the n is even it is not a generator and if it is odd it is a generator.","response_history":["if i t is eve n and the g","if it is even and the n is even it is not a generator and if it is po","if it is even and the n is even it is not a generator and if it is p","if it is even and the n is even it is not a generator and if it is odd it is a generator."],"rt":23302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":778096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":13788,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":791889,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":796542,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":7534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":804082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False because when you multiply it out it could be a generator or not","response_history":["False because when you multiply it out it could be either ","False because when you multiply it out it could be ei","False because  when yo u multiply it out it could be e","False because when you multiply it out it could be a generator or not"],"rt":44759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":848845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":855581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"It's never a generator because you cou ld have  a value that produces 0.","response_history":["It's never  ","It's never a generator because you cuold ","It's never a generator because you cuold","It's never a generator because you cuol","It's never a generator because you cuo","It's never a generator because you cu","It's never a generator because you c","It's never a generator because you ou","It's never a generator because you o","It's never a generator because you could have a vlue that produces 0.","It's never a generator because you could have a value that produces 0."],"rt":32018,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":887603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":5763,"trial_type":" question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":893371,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1899,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":895274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"30","response_history":["30"],"rt":3275,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":898553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachel ors Degr ee"],"rt":2839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":901394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"pre calculus in high school and statistics in college.","response_history":["pre calculus in high school and statistics in college."],"rt":16824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":918221,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never h eard of  it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3403,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":921627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":925291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5065,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":930362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":933323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":936007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":938463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":4035,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":942503,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":946212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"it was hard","response_history":["it was hard"],"rt":4835,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":951050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]